A Guide to the Department of Confederate Military Records, 1859-1996
Library of Virginia
- Series II: Unit Records
  - Subseries 3: Infantry
    - Regiments
      - 31st
        - Co. B (2nd) (Bradshaw's Co.) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 8), 1861-1913 (Box 24, Folder 35)
        - Co. C (Turner's Co.), 1862-1897 (Box 24, Folder 36)
        - Co. D (Gilmer Rifles), n.d. (Box 24, Folder 37)
        - Co. E (The Highlanders) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 8), 1862-1904 (Box 24, Folder 38)
        - Co. F (Currence's Co.), 1897 (Box 24, Folder 39)
        - Co. G (Arbogast's Co.), 1897 (Box 24, Folder 40)
        - Co. H (Reger's Co.), 1897 (Box 24, Folder 41)
        - Co. I (Jackson's Co.) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 8), 1862-1897 (Box 24, Folder 42)
        - Co. K (Sturn's Co.), 1897 (Box 24, Folder 43)
        - Miscellaneous, 1861-1905 (Box 24, Folder 44)
      - 32nd
        - Co. A (Wythe Rifles) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 8), 1861 (Box 24, Folder 45)
        - Co. C (Williamsburg Junior Guard), 1890-1910 (Box 24, Folder 46)
        - Co. E (Hampton Greys), n.d. (Box 24, Folder 47)
        - Co. F (Nelson Guards), n.d. (Box 24, Folder 48)
        - Co. H (2nd) (Warwick Beauregards) (See Also Oversized - Box 5), 1884-1903 (Box 24, Folder 49)
        - Co. I (2nd) (York Rangers), 1862-1916 (Box 24, Folder 50)
        - Co. K (2nd) (Lee Guards), n.d. (Box 24, Folder 51)
      - 33rd
        - Co. A (Potomac Guards), n.d. (Box 24, Folder 52)
        - Co. B (Toms Brook Guard), 1913 (Box 24, Folder 53)
        - Co. C (Tenth Legion Minute Men), 1861-1915 (Box 24, Folder 54)
        - Co. G (Mount Jackson Rifles) (See Also Oversized - Box 5), 1912 (Box 24, Folder 55)
        - Co. I (Rockingham Confederates), n.d. (Box 24, Folder 56)
        - Miscellaneous, 1906 (Box 24, Folder 57)
      - 34th
        - Co. A (Gloucester Artillery) (See Also Oversized - Box 5) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 8), 1861-1916 (Box 24, Folder 58)
        - Co. B (Mecklenburg Heavy Arty), n.d. (Box 24, Folder 59)
        - Co. D (Green Rough & Readys) (See Also Oversized - Box 5), 1884-1920 (Box 24, Folder 60)
        - Co. E (Piedmont Battery) (See Also Oversized - Box 5) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 8), 1861-1920 (Box 24, Folder 61)
        - Co. G (Jordon's Co.) (See Also Oversized - Box 5), 1884-1913 (Box 24, Folder 62)
        - Co. H (Luck's Co.) (See Also Oversized - Box 5), 1884-1920 (Box 24, Folder 63)
        - Co. I (Sale's Co.), 1910 (Box 24, Folder 64)
        - Co. K (Bagby's Co.) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 8), 1861-1905 (Box 24, Folder 65)
        - Miscellaneous, 1908-1934 (Box 24, Folder 66)
      - 36th
        - Co. A (Buffalo Guards), 1907 (Box 25, Folder 1)
        - Co. B (2nd) (Boone Rangers), n.d. (Box 25, Folder 2)
        - Co. C (2nd) (Raleigh Rangers), 1861-1906 (Box 25, Folder 3)
        - Co. D (2nd) (Lawson's Co.), n.d. (Box 25, Folder 4)
        - Co. E (1st & 2nd) (Raleigh Rangers) (Western Riflemen) (See Also Oversized - Box 5) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 8), 1861-1862 (Box 25, Folder 5)
        - Co. F (Mountain Riflemen), n.d. (Box 25, Folder 6)
        - Co. G (2nd) (Harner's Co.), 1910 (Box 25, Folder 7)
        - Co. H (2nd) (Porterfield's Co.), n.d. (Box 25, Folder 8)
        - Co. I (3rd) (Gott's Co.), n.d. (Box 25, Folder 9)
        - Miscellaneous, 1862-1905 (Box 25, Folder 10)
      - 37th
        - Co. B (Virginia Mountain Boys) (See Oversized - Box 5), 1884 (Box 25, Folder 11)
        - Co. C (McElhenny's Co.) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 8), 1861 (Box 25, Folder 12)
        - Co. D (Wood's Co.) (See Also Oversized - Box 5), 1884 (Box 25, Folder 13)
        - Co. E (Gibson's Co.), 1884 (Box 25, Folder 14)
        - Co. F (Glade Spring Rifle Co.), n.d. (Box 25, Folder 15)
        - Co. G (Kendrick's Co.), n.d. (Box 25, Folder 16)
        - Co. H (King's Mountain Rifles), n.d. (Box 25, Folder 17)
        - Co. I (New Garden Fearnots), n.d. (Box 25, Folder 18)
        - Co. K (Washington Independents) (See Also Oversized - Box 5), 1884-1914 (Box 25, Folder 19)
        - Miscellaneous, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 20)
      - 38th
        - Co. A (Townes' Co.) (See Also Oversized - Box 5), 1861-1900 (Box 25, Folder 21)
        - Co. B (Cabell's (John) Co.) (See Also Oversized - Box 5) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 8), 1861-1864 (Box 25, Folder 22)
        - Co. C (Simpson's Co.) (See Also Oversized - Box 5), 1861-1862 (Box 25, Folder 23)
        - Co. D (Laurel Green Riflemen) (See Also Oversized - Box 5), 1861-1862 (Box 25, Folder 24)
        - Co. E (Cabell's (Joseph) Co.) (See Also Oversized - Box 5) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 8), 1861-1863 (Box 25, Folder 25)
        - Co. F (Davis Rifle Guard) (See Also Oversized - Box 5) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 8), 1861-1884 (Box 25, Folder 26)
        - Co. G (Mecklenburg Rifles) (See Also Oversized - Box 5) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 8), 1861-1913 (Box 25, Folder 27)
        - Co. H (Secession Guards) (See Also Oversized - Box 5), 1861-1910 (Box 25, Folder 28)
        - Co. I (2nd) (Wood's Co.) (See Also Oversized - Box 5) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 8), 1861-1864 (Box 25, Folder 29)
        - Co. K (Cascade Rifles) (See Also Oversized - Box 5) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 8), 1861-1913 (Box 25, Folder 30)
        - Miscellaneous (See Also Oversized - Box 5) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 8), 1861-1907 (Box 25, Folder 31)
      - 39th
        - Co. A (Wickings' Co.) (See Misc.), 1909 (Box 25, Folder 32)
        - Co. B (Ironmonger's Co.), 1909 (Box 25, Folder 33)
        - Co. D (Kellam's Co.), 1909 (Box 25, Folder 34)
        - Co. I (LeCato's Co.), 1904 (Box 25, Folder 35)
        - Miscellaneous, 1904-1909 (Box 25, Folder 36)
      - 40th
        - Field & Staff (See Also Oversized - Drawer 9), 1863 (Box 25, Folder 37)
        - Co. A (Wicomico Artillery) (See Also Oversized - Box 6) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 9), 1863-1884 (Box 25, Folder 38)
        - Co. B (Totuskey Grays) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 9), 1863 (Box 25, Folder 39)
        - Co. C (Heathsville Guards) (See Also Oversized - Box 6) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 9), 1863-1884 (Box 25, Folder 40)
        - Co. D (Farmer's Fork Grays) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 9), 1863 (Box 25, Folder 41)
        - Co. E (Pitt's Co.) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 9), 1863-1921 (Box 25, Folder 42)
        - Co. F (Cundiff's Co.) (See Also Oversized - Box 6) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 9), 1863-1920 (Box 25, Folder 43)
        - Co. G (Northumberland Rifles) (See Oversized - Box 6) (See Oversized - Drawer 9), 1863-1884 (Box 25, Folder 44)
        - Co. H (Lancaster Grays) (See Oversized - Box 6) (See Oversized - Drawer 9), 1863-1884 (Box 25, Folder 45)
        - Co. I (Robinson Guards) (See Also Oversized - Box 6) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 9), 1863-1884 (Box 25, Folder 46)
        - Co. K (Potomac Rifles) (See Also Oversized - Box 6) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 9), 1863-1884 (Box 25, Folder 47)
        - Miscellaneous, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 48)
      - 41st
        - Co. A (Eppes' Co.), n.d. (Box 25, Folder 49)
        - Co. B (Confederate Grays), 1914 (Box 25, Folder 50)
        - Co. C (McRae Rifle Guards), 1912 (Box 25, Folder 51)
        - Co. D (Rough & Ready Volunteers), 1904 (Box 25, Folder 52)
        - Co. E (2nd) (Confederate Cadets), n.d. (Box 25, Folder 53)
        - Co. F (Norfolk Co. Rifle Patriots) (See Oversized - Box 6), 1912 (Box 25, Folder 54)
        - Co. G (2nd) (Ragland Guard), 1911 (Box 25, Folder 55)
        - Co. I (Cypress Chapel Sharpshooters), n.d. (Box 25, Folder 56)
        - Miscellaneous, 1862-1894 (Box 25, Folder 57)
      - 42nd
        - Co. B (Floyd Guards) (See Also Oversized - Box 6), 1884-1913 (Box 25, Folder 58)
        - Co. C (Buford Grays) (See Also Oversized - Box 6) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 10), 1861-1900 (Box 25, Folder 59)
        - Co. D (Campbell-Lee Guards), 1908 (Box 25, Folder 60)
        - Co. E (Dixie Greys) (See Also Oversized - Box 6) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 10), 1861-1900 (Box 25, Folder 61)
        - Co. H (Patrick Henry Volunteers), 1913 (Box 25, Folder 62)
        - Co. I (Campbell Guards), n.d. (Box 25, Folder 63)
        - Miscellaneous (See Also Oversized - Drawer 10), 1861-1862 (Box 25, Folder 64)
      - 44th
        - Co. A (Appomattox Invincibles), 1906 (Box 26, Folder 1)
        - Co. B (Byrd Rifles), n.d. (Box 26, Folder 2)
        - Co. C (Travis Rifles) (See Also Oversized - Box 6), ca. 1861-1906 (Box 26, Folder 3)
        - Co. D (Ambler Grays), 1905 (Box 26, Folder 4)
        - Co. E (Richmond Zouaves), 1862 (Box 26, Folder 5)
        - Co. F (Fluvanna Hornets) (See Also Oversized - Box 6), 1900 (Box 26, Folder 6)
        - Co. G (Randolph Guard) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 10), 1861-1906 (Box 26, Folder 7)
        - Co. H (Amelia Minute Men) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 10), 1861-1911 (Box 26, Folder 8)
        - Co. I (Mossingford Rifles), n.d. (Box 26, Folder 9)
        - Co. K (Fluvanna Guards) (See Also Oversized - Box 6), 1884-1912 (Box 26, Folder 10)
        - Co. L, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 11)
        - Miscellaneous (See Also Oversized - Drawer 10), 1861 (Box 26, Folder 12)
      - 45th
        - Co. A (Floyd Guard), 1913 (Box 26, Folder 13)
        - Co. B (Mount Airy Rough & Readys), n.d. (Box 26, Folder 14)
        - Co. C (Grayson Rifles), 1909-1913 (Box 26, Folder 15)
        - Co. D (Minute Men), n.d. (Box 26, Folder 16)
        - Co. E (Rough and Readys) (See Also Oversized - Box 6), 1884-1885 (Box 26, Folder 17)
        - Co. F (Sharpshooters), n.d. (Box 26, Folder 18)
        - Co. K (Tazewell Boys), 1915 (Box 26, Folder 19)
        - Miscellaneous, 1884 (Box 26, Folder 20)
      - 46th
        - Co. A (Richmond Light Infantry Blues) (See Also Oversized - Box 6) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 10), 1864-1884 (Box 26, Folder 21)
        - Co. B (2nd) (Liberty Guards), 1884 (Box 26, Folder 22)
        - Co. C (2nd) (Pig River Invincibles), n.d. (Box 26, Folder 23)
        - Co. D (2nd) (Border Guards), 1909 (Box 26, Folder 24)
        - Co. E (2nd) (Scottsville Greys), n.d. (Box 26, Folder 25)
        - Co. F (4th) (Eastern Shore Refugees) (See Also Oversized - Box 6) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 10), 1864-1914 (Box 26, Folder 26)
        - Co. G (1st) (Albemarle Jackson Avengers), n.d. (Box 26, Folder 27)
        - Co. H (2nd) (Goochland Infantry), n.d. (Box 26, Folder 28)
        - Co. I (2nd) (Green Mountain Greys), 1913 (Box 26, Folder 29)
        - Co. K (2nd) (Orange County Minute Men), n.d. (Box 26, Folder 30)
        - Miscellaneous, 1864-1913 (Box 26, Folder 31)
      - 47th
        - Co. A (Green's Co.) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 10), 1862-1884 (Box 26, Folder 32)
        - Co. B (Tayloe's Co.) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 10), 1862 (Box 26, Folder 33)
        - Co. C (Wharton's Co.) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 10), 1862 (Box 26, Folder 34)
        - Co. D (Lyell's Co.) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 10), 1862-1907 (Box 26, Folder 35)
        - Co. E (Port Royal Guards) (See Oversized - Drawer 10), 1862 (Box 26, Folder 36)
        - Co. F (Lacey Rifles) (See Oversized - Drawer 10), 1862 (Box 26, Folder 37)
        - Co. G (Wright's Co.) (See Oversized - Drawer 10), 1862 (Box 26, Folder 38)
        - Co. H (3rd) (Welch's Co.) (See Oversized - Drawer 10), 1862 (Box 26, Folder 39)
        - Co. I (3rd) (Stafford Guards) (See Oversized - Drawer 10), 1862-1863 (Box 26, Folder 40)
        - Co. K (2nd) (Tyranny Unmasked Artillery) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 10), 1862 (Box 26, Folder 41)
        - Miscellaneous, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 42)
      - 48th
        - Co. A (Stock Creek Greys), n.d. (Box 26, Folder 43)
        - Co. B (Campbell Guards), n.d. (Box 26, Folder 44)
        - Co. C (Osborne Ford Independents), 1912 (Box 26, Folder 45)
        - Co. D (Smyth Rifle Greys), n.d. (Box 26, Folder 46)
        - Co. E (Nickelsville Spartan Band), n.d. (Box 26, Folder 47)
        - Co. F (Holston Foresters), n.d. (Box 26, Folder 48)
        - Co. G (Lee County Guards), n.d. (Box 26, Folder 49)
        - Co. I (Mountain Marksmen), n.d. (Box 26, Folder 50)
        - Co. K (Russell Guards), n.d. (Box 26, Folder 51)
        - Miscellaneous, 1915 (Box 26, Folder 52)
      - 49th
        - Co. A (Ewell Guards) (See Also Oversized - Box 6), 1900-1906 (Box 26, Folder 53)
        - Co. B (Quantico Guards) (See Also Oversized - Box 6), 1900-1906 (Box 26, Folder 54)
        - Co. C (Fauquier Guards) (See Also Oversized - Box 6) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 11), 1863-1906 (Box 26, Folder 55)
        - Co. D (Warren Blues) (See Also Oversized - Box 6), 1900-1904 (Box 26, Folder 56)
        - Co. E (Flint Hill Rifles), n.d. (Box 26, Folder 57)
        - Co. F (Crowder's Co.), 1911 (Box 26, Folder 58)
        - Co. G (3rd) (Rappahannock Rifles), n.d. (Box 26, Folder 59)
        - Co. H (New Market Volunteers) (See Also Oversized - Box 6), 1884-1912 (Box 26, Folder 60)
        - Co. I (Amherst Rough & Readys), n.d. (Box 26, Folder 61)
        - Co. K (Sperryville Sharp Shooters) (See Also Oversized - Box 6), 1864-1906 (Box 26, Folder 62)
        - Miscellaneous, 1911-1930 (Box 26, Folder 63)
      - 50th
        - Co. A (Richmond's Co.), n.d. (Box 27, Folder 1)
        - Co. B (Vandeventer's Co.), n.d. (Box 27, Folder 2)
        - Co. C (Kelley's Co.), n.d. (Box 27, Folder 3)
        - Co. D (Wilson Rifles), 1913 (Box 27, Folder 4)
        - Co. E (Smyth Grays), n.d. (Box 27, Folder 5)
        - Co. F (Snead's Co.), 1913 (Box 27, Folder 6)
        - Co. G (2nd) (Hannah's Co.), n.d. (Box 27, Folder 7)
        - Co. I (Poage's Co.), 1913 (Box 27, Folder 8)
        - Co. K (Lawson's Co.), 1914 (Box 27, Folder 9)
        - Miscellaneous, 1913 (Box 27, Folder 10)
      - 51st
        - Co. A (Wolfe's Co.), n.d. (Box 27, Folder 11)
        - Co. B (Wharton Grays), 1907-1915 (Box 27, Folder 12)
        - Co. C (Wythe Rifles), 1914 (Box 27, Folder 13)
        - Co. D (Ross' Co.), 1916 (Box 27, Folder 14)
        - Co. E (Nelson Volunteers), n.d. (Box 27, Folder 15)
        - Co. F (Bland Tigers), n.d. (Box 27, Folder 16)
        - Co. G (Floyd Game Cocks) (See Also Oversized - Box 6) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 11), 1861-1913 (Box 27, Folder 17)
        - Co. H (Conner's Co.), 1900 (Box 27, Folder 18)
        - Co. I (Young's Co.), 1913 (Box 27, Folder 19)
        - Co. K (Dickey's Co.) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 11), 1861 (Box 27, Folder 20)
      - 52nd
        - Co. A (Augusta Fencibles), n.d. (Box 27, Folder 21)
        - Co. B (1st) (McDowell Guard), n.d. (Box 27, Folder 22)
        - Co. C (Letcher Guard), n.d. (Box 27, Folder 23)
        - Co. D (Hottel's Co.), n.d. (Box 27, Folder 24)
        - Co. F (Cline's Co.), 1911-1912 (Box 27, Folder 25)
        - Co. G (McCune's Co.) (See Also Oversized - Box 6) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 11), 1862-1900 (Box 27, Folder 26)
        - Co. H (Staunton Pioneers), 1913 (Box 27, Folder 27)
        - Co. I (Men of West Augusta), n.d. (Box 27, Folder 28)
        - Miscellaneous, 1905 (Box 27, Folder 29)
      - 53rd
        - Co. A (Halifax Light Infantry) (See Also Oversized - Box 6), 1884-1905 (Box 27, Folder 30)
        - Co. B (Barhamsville Greys) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 11), 1861 (Box 27, Folder 31)
        - Co. C (Old Dominion Riflemen), n.d. (Box 27, Folder 32)
        - Co. D (Taylor Grays), n.d. (Box 27, Folder 33)
        - Co. E (Pamunkey Rifles), 1916 (Box 27, Folder 34)
        - Co. F (Edmunds Guards), 1913 (Box 27, Folder 35)
        - Co. G (Logan Guards), 1904-1908 (Box 27, Folder 36)
        - Co. H (Mattopany Guards), 1894-1909 (Box 27, Folder 37)
        - Co. I (Chatham Grays) (See Also Oversized - Box 6) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 11), 1861-1863 (Box 27, Folder 38)
        - Co. K (Charles City Southern Guards), 1903 (Box 27, Folder 39)
        - Miscellaneous, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 40)
      - 54th
        - Co. A (Dickerson's Co.) (See Also Oversized - Box 6), 1900 (Box 27, Folder 41)
        - Co. B (Godbey's Co.) (See Also Oversized - Box 6), 1884-1900 (Box 27, Folder 42)
        - Co. C (Taylor's Co.), n.d. (Box 27, Folder 43)
        - Co. D (Harman's Co.) (See Also Oversized - Box 6), 1884-1931 (Box 27, Folder 44)
        - Co. E (Montgomery Greys), 1905-1908 (Box 27, Folder 45)
        - Co. F (Jordan's Co.) (See Also Oversized - Box 6) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 11), 1863-1904 (Box 27, Folder 46)
        - Co. G (Spencer's Co.), n.d. (Box 27, Folder 47)
        - Co. H (Griffith's Co.) (See Also Oversized - Box 6), 1900 (Box 27, Folder 48)
        - Co. I (Akers' Co.) (See Also Oversized - Box 6), 1900 (Box 27, Folder 49)
        - Co. K (Deyerle's Co.) (See Also Oversized - Box 6), n.d. (Box 27, Folder 50)
        - Miscellaneous, 1904-1905 (Box 27, Folder 51)
      - 55th
        - Co. A (Essex Artillery), 1909 (Box 27, Folder 52)
        - Co. B (Middlesex Artillery), n.d. (Box 27, Folder 53)
        - Co. C (Middlesex Southerners), 1912-1919 (Box 27, Folder 54)
        - Co. D (Essex Davis Rifles) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 11), 1864-1911 (Box 27, Folder 55)
        - Co. E (Westmoreland Greys), n.d. (Box 27, Folder 56)
        - Co. F (Essex Sharpshooters), 1897-1913 (Box 27, Folder 57)
        - Co. G (Essex Greys), n.d. (Box 27, Folder 58)
        - Co. H (Middlesex Rifles), n.d. (Box 27, Folder 59)
        - Co. I (Barrick's Co.), n.d. (Box 27, Folder 60)
        - Co. K (Broocke's Co.), n.d. (Box 27, Folder 61)
        - Co. L (Lawson's Co.), n.d. (Box 27, Folder 62)
        - Co. M (Alexander's Co.), n.d. (Box 27, Folder 63)
        - Miscellaneous, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 64)
      - 56th
        - Co. A (Mecklenburg Guards), 1900-1913 (Box 28, Folder 1)
        - Co. B (Mecklenburg Spartans), 1900 (Box 28, Folder 2)
        - Co. C (Louisa Holliday Guards), 1912 (Box 28, Folder 3)
        - Co. D (Buckingham Yancey Guards), n.d. (Box 28, Folder 4)
        - Co. E (Ebenezer Greys), 1863-1908 (Box 28, Folder 5)
        - Co. F (Louisa Nelson Greys), 1905 (Box 28, Folder 6)
        - Co. G (Charlotte Defenders), 1904-1921 (Box 28, Folder 7)
        - Co. H (White Hall Guards), 1911 (Box 28, Folder 8)
        - Co. I (Charlotte Greys), 1897-1921 (Box 28, Folder 9)
        - Co. K (Harrison's Guards), n.d. (Box 28, Folder 10)
        - Miscellaneous, 1905-1913 (Box 28, Folder 11)
      - 57th
        - Co. A (Jeff Davis Guard) (See Also Oversized - Box 6), 1884-1913 (Box 28, Folder 12)
        - Co. B (Franklin Sharpshooters) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 11), 1861-1910 (Box 28, Folder 13)
        - Co. C (Franklin Fire Eaters), n.d. (Box 28, Folder 14)
        - Co. D (Galveston Tigers), n.d. (Box 28, Folder 15)
        - Co. E (Pig River Greys), n.d. (Box 28, Folder 16)
        - Co. F (Henry & Pittsylvania Rifles), n.d. (Box 28, Folder 17)
        - Co. G (Ladies Guard), 1913 (Box 28, Folder 18)
        - Co. H (Rivanna Guards), 1862-1911 (Box 28, Folder 19)
        - Co. I (Pittsylvania Life Guards), 1884 (Box 28, Folder 20)
        - Co. K (Botetourt Guards) (See Also Oversized - Box 6), 1903 (Box 28, Folder 21)
        - Miscellaneous, 1884-1905 (Box 28, Folder 22)
      - 58th
        - Co. A (Walker Guards), 1911 (Box 28, Folder 23)
        - Co. B (Stewartville Tigers) (See Also Oversized - Box 6), 1884 (Box 28, Folder 24)
        - Co. C (Big Island Greys), n.d. (Box 28, Folder 25)
        - Co. D (Booth's Co.), n.d. (Box 28, Folder 26)
        - Co. E (Hale's Ford Franklin Guard), 1884 (Box 28, Folder 27)
        - Co. F (Amherst Johnson Guard), n.d. (Box 28, Folder 28)
        - Co. G (Kerr's Creek Confederates), 1914 (Box 28, Folder 29)
        - Co. H (Booker's Co.), n.d. (Box 28, Folder 30)
        - Co. I (Staunton Yeomanry) (See Also Oversized - Box 6), 1884 (Box 28, Folder 31)
        - Co. K (Kasey's Co.) (See Oversized - Box 6), 1884 (Box 28, Folder 32)
        - Miscellaneous, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 33)
      - 59th
        - Co. A (2nd) (Ben McCulloch Rangers), 1912 (Box 28, Folder 34)
        - Co. B (3rd) (Brunswick Blues), n.d. (Box 28, Folder 35)
        - Co. C (2nd) (Red Sulpher Yankee Hunters) (See Also Oversized - Box 6), 1913 (Box 28, Folder 36)
        - Co. D (3rd) (Jackson Guard), n.d. (Box 28, Folder 37)
        - Co. E (Bruce Guards), 1912-1916 (Box 28, Folder 38)
        - Co. F (3rd) (Richmond Light Guard), 1916 (Box 28, Folder 39)
        - Co. G (2nd) (University Volunteers), 1900-1914 (Box 28, Folder 40)
        - Co. H (2nd) (Lunenburg Heavy Arty), 1900 (Box 28, Folder 41)
        - Co. I, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 42)
        - Co. K (2nd) (Charleston Sharpshooters), n.d. (Box 28, Folder 43)
        - Miscellaneous, 1906 (Box 28, Folder 44)
      - 60th
        - Co. A (Beirne Sharpshooters) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 11), 1861-1929 (Box 28, Folder 45)
        - Co. B (Greenbrier Mountain Rifles) (See Also Oversized - Box 6) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 11), 1861-1884 (Box 28, Folder 46)
        - Co. D (Alleghany Rifles), 1884 (Box 28, Folder 47)
        - Co. F (James River Rifles), 1911 (Box 28, Folder 48)
        - Co. H (2nd) (Pack's Co.), n.d. (Box 28, Folder 49)
        - Co. I (Ryan's Co.), n.d. (Box 28, Folder 50)
        - Co. K (Osceola Guards) (See Also Oversized - Box 6), n.d. (Box 28, Folder 51)
        - Miscellaneous (See Also Oversized - Box 6), 1862-1913 (Box 28, Folder 52)
      - 61st
        - Co. A (Jackson's Grays), n.d. (Box 28, Folder 53)
        - Co. B (Wilson Guard) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 11), 1864-1884 (Box 28, Folder 54)
        - Co. D (Jackson Light Infantry), n.d. (Box 28, Folder 55)
        - Co. F (Isle of Wight Avengers), n.d. (Box 28, Folder 56)
        - Co. G (Confederate Defenders), n.d. (Box 28, Folder 57)
        - Co. I (Billsoly Blues), n.d. (Box 28, Folder 58)
        - Miscellaneous, 1865-1884 (Box 28, Folder 59)
      - 62nd
        - Co. A (2nd) (Hall's Co.), 1910 (Box 28, Folder 60)
        - Co. B (2nd) (Hardy Blues), 1912 (Box 28, Folder 61)
        - Co. C (2nd) Nelson's Co.), n.d. (Box 28, Folder 62)
        - Co. E (2nd) (Hill's Co.), n.d. (Box 28, Folder 63)
        - Co. F (2nd) (Franklin Guards) (See Also Oversized - Box 6) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 11), 1864-1905 (Box 28, Folder 64)
        - Co. G (2nd) (Currence's Co.), 1911 (Box 28, Folder 65)
        - Co. H (2nd) (Carlin's Co.), 1915 (Box 28, Folder 66)
        - Co. I (2nd) (Pendleton Rifles), 1913 (Box 28, Folder 67)
        - Co. K (2nd) (Carrickhoff's Co.) (See Also Oversized - Box 6), 1909 (Box 28, Folder 68)
        - Co. N & O (Muse's & Monroe's Co.), n.d. (Box 28, Folder 69)
        - Miscellaneous (See Also Oversized - Box 6), 1908-1913 (Box 28, Folder 70)
      - 63rd
        - Co. A (Hunter's Co.), 1913 (Box 29, Folder 1)
        - Co. B (Lynch's Co.), n.d. (Box 29, Folder 2)
        - Co. C (Cornutt's Co.), 1900-1916 (Box 29, Folder 3)
        - Co. D (Francis' Co.), n.d. (Box 29, Folder 4)
        - Co. E (Rush's Co.), n.d. (Box 29, Folder 5)
        - Co. F (Snodgrass' Co.), n.d. (Box 29, Folder 6)
        - Co. G (Hampton's Co.), 1900 (Box 29, Folder 7)
        - Co. H (Keesling's Co.), n.d. (Box 29, Folder 8)
        - Co. I (2nd) (Martin's Co.) (See Also Oversized - Box 6), 1884 (Box 29, Folder 9)
        - Co. K (Killinger's Co.), n.d. (Box 29, Folder 10)
        - Miscellaneous, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 11)
      - 64th
        - Co. A (Hobbs' Co.), n.d. (Box 29, Folder 12)
        - Co. B (Boles' Co.), n.d. (Box 29, Folder 13)
        - Co. C (Webb's Co.), n.d. (Box 29, Folder 14)
        - Co. D (Day's Co.), n.d. (Box 29, Folder 15)
        - Co. E (Gray's Co.), n.d. (Box 29, Folder 16)
        - Co. F (1st) (Ratliff's Co.), n.d. (Box 29, Folder 17)
        - Co. G (Wynn's Co.), n.d. (Box 29, Folder 18)
        - Co. H (Creech's Co.), n.d. (Box 29, Folder 19)
        - Co. I (Collier's Co.), n.d. (Box 29, Folder 20)
        - Co. K (Tyler's Co.), n.d. (Box 29, Folder 21)
        - Miscellaneous, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 22)
    - Battalions
      - 1st (Irish)